Guide to the Martha Wilson Papers, 1950-2021 (bulk 1964-2006) MSS.175
Fales Library and Special Collections
Martha Wilson Papers
1950-2021
1964-2006
Fales Library and Special Collections
Wilson, Martha, 1947-
MSS.175
92 Linear Feet in 103 containers
3 DVDs
700 Megabytes in one computer disc.
The Martha Wilson Papers consist of comprehensive documentation of the life and career of Martha Wilson, artist and Founding Director of Franklin Furnace, Inc. Materials include journals, correspondence, flyers and posters, articles, clippings, juvenilia dating from grade school onward, video recordings, and a computer disc. The collection also contains materials related to Wilson's son Comly Cook-Wilson, and restricted materials dealing with Wilson's finances and medical history.
Conditions Governing Access
Series V. Medical and Finacial Files, Series III. Subject Files - Subseries G: Poconos House, and a few files containing student records are restricted. Researchers should contact special.collections@nyu.edu for more information.
The remainder of the collection is open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Martha Wilson in 2006. The accession number associated with this gift is 2006.175. Further accretions were donated in 2008-2022. The accession numbers associated with these gifts are 2008.175, 2010.175, 2011.175, 2013.175.001, 2013.175.002, 2015.175, 2017.027, 2018.093, 2020.008, and 2023.011.
Arrangement
Where possible original order was maintained, especially in the subject files. However, this collection had little original order; where the original arrangement was unclear, items were arranged in chronological or alphabetical order.
Journals are arranged in chronological order. Correspondence and subject files (where appropriate) are arranged alphabetically. Flyers and clippings are in chronological order.
The Collection has been arranged into nine series:
Series I: Journals
Series II: Correspondence
Series III: Subject Files
Series IV: Juvenilia
Series V: Medical and Financial Files (Restricted)
Series VI: Flyers, Invitations and Programs
Series VII: Clippings, Articles and Magazines
Series VIII: Objects
Series IX: Bibliographic Materials
Some items were removed to oversize boxes, and are listed at the end of the finding aid.
Biographical Note
Martha Wilson is an artist and the Founding Director of Franklin Furnace Archive, Inc., a multifaceted arts organization active from 1976 to the present. Born in Philadelphia in 1947, Wilson attended The George School in Newtown, Pennsylvania and graduated from Ohio's Wilmington College in 1969. She attended graduate school at Dalhousie University in Halifax, Nova Scotia where she received her M.A. in English Literature in 1971. She completed one year of doctoral studies at Dalhousie (leaving after a dispute with her dissertation advisor) and taught English at the Nova Scotia College of Art and Design (NASCAD) from 1972-1974. Wilson began her work as a performance and conceptual artist in Nova Scotia and found early recognition when her piece Breast Forms Permutated (1974) was included in Lucy Lippard's show of conceptual art by women, c. 7500, at the California Institute of the Arts.
Wilson moved to New York City in 1974 and performed at venues such as The Kitchen, The Whitney, Hallwalls (Buffalo), and P.S. 1. In 1976 Wilson founded Franklin Furnace in her loft on Franklin Street in TriBeCA as a space for the display of artists' books. In 1978 Wilson joined DisBAND, an all-female conceptual band with artists Ilona Granet, Donna Henes, Ingrid Sischy, and Diane Torr (at various times also including Barbara Ess, Daile Kaplan, and Barbara Kruger.) During this time Franklin Furnace was developing not only as a place for artists' books, but for temporary installation art and performance art, eventually presenting artists such as Ida Applebroog, Eric Bogosian, David Cale, Patty Chang, Guillermo Gomez-Pena, Ann Hamilton, Murray Hill, Jenny Holzer, Barbara Kruger, Sherrie Levine, Liza Lou, Robbie McCauley, William Pope.L, Paul Zaloom, and three of the so-named NEA 4: Karen Finley, Holly Hughes, and John Fleck. The Furnace's performance space was closed in 1990 after a citation for being an illegal social club leading to its first season in exile at Judson Memorial Church. In 1993 Franklin Furnace's collection of artists' books from 1960 on, at the time the largest such collection in the world, was acquired by the Museum of Modern Art. In 1997 The Furnace sold its loft space in TriBeCa and became a virtual institution existing primarily on the Internet.
In her own art work Wilson is known for her satirical portrayals of Nancy Reagan, Barbara Bush, and Tipper Gore. Wilson received National Endowment for the Arts Fellowships in Performance Art in 1978 and 1983, the Skowhegan School Governor's Award for Service to the Arts in 1991, an Obie Award in 1992 for commitment to artists' freedom of expression and a Bessie for commitment to artists' freedom of expression in 1992. In 2001 Wilson received a New York Foundation of the Arts Fellowship in Performance Art. More recently her work has been seen at venues such as White Columns in New York (Gloria: Another Look at Feminist Art in the 1970s, 2002) and the Museum of Contemporary Art in Los Angeles (2007 WACK! Art and the Feminist Revolution).
Sources:
Goldberg, RoseLee. Performance: Live Art, 1909 to the Present. New York: Harry N. Abrams, Inc., 1979.
Jones, Amelia, editor. Sexual Politics: Judy Chicago's Dinner Party in Feminist Art History. Los Angeles: University of California Press, 1996.
Lippard, Lucy R. The Pink Glass Swan: Selected Feminist Essays on Art. New York: The New Press, 1995.
Reckitt, Helena and Peggy Phelan. Art and Feminism: Themes and Movements. London: Phaidon Press, 2001.
Rosen, Randy, and Catherine C. Brawer. Making Their Mark: Women Artists Move into the Mainstream, 1970-1985. New York: Abbeville Press, 1989.
Stiles, Kristine and Peter Selz, eds. Theories and Documents of Contemporary Art: A Sourcebook of Artists' Writings. Berkeley: University of California Press, 1996.
Wark, Jayne, "Martha Wilson: Not Taking It at Face Value," Camera Obscura: Feminism, Culture and Media Studies. Durham, N.C.: Duke University Press, 2001.
---"Conceptual Art and Feminism: Martha Rosler, Adrian Piper, Eleanor Antin, and Martha Wilson": Woman's Art Journal, Vol. 22, No. 1 Spring - Summer, 2001.
Selected Performances and Exhibitions
The Martha Wilson Papers consist of comprehensive documentation of the life and career of Martha Wilson. Materials include journals, correspondence, flyers and posters, articles, clippings and juvenilia dating from 1950 on. The collection also contains restricted materials dealing with Wilson's finances and medical history. The following are performances and exhibitions for which the collection contains materials:
2007 WACK! Art and the Feminist Revolution, Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles
2006 The Downtown Show, Grey Art Gallery, New York University, New York
2005 How American Women Artists Invented Post-Modernism, Mason Gross School of the Arts, Rutgers University, New Brunswick, New Jersey
2003 Separated at Birth, StART Festival, Judson Church, New York City
2002 Personal & Political, Guild Hall Museum, East Hampton, New York
2002 Gloria: Another Look at Feminist Art in the 1970s, White Columns, New York City
1994 Tipper Gore's Advice for the 90s, window installation at Printed Matter, New York City
1992 Barbara Bush On Abuse, Cooper Union, New York City
1985 Just Say No to Arms Control, performance in the guise of Nancy Reagan for Brother Ron's Gospel Hour, New York City
1980 DISBAND at Spazio Zero, Rome, Italy
1976 Queen, Whitney Museum of American Art, New York City
1975 De-Formation, performance in Autogeography show, Downtown Whitney, New York City
1973 Transformance: Claudia, collaborative performance with Jacki Apple at The Plaza Hotel, New York City
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact special.collections@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Born-Digital Access Policies and Procedures
Born-digital materials have not been transferred and may not be available to researchers. Researchers may request access copies. To request that material be transferred, or if you are unsure if material has been transferred, please contact special.collections@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Scope and Contents
The Martha Wilson Papers consist of materials related to the life and career of Martha Wilson. The bulk of the collection is comprised of Wilson's journals from 1969 to 2017, correspondence from 1964 to 2013 and a large collection of flyers and invitations. Subject files related to Wilson's life, art, and work also comprise a significant part of the collection. These materials span the years from 1960-2011. Strengths of the collection include the large amount of correspondence between Wilson and her family, and materials related to art projects and intellectual collaborations. There collection also contains a few video recordings and one computer disc.
Materials date from 1950 to 2017 with the bulk of the materials covering 1964 to 2006.
Artists -- New York (N.Y.); Alternative spaces (Arts facilities); Feminism and art.; Performance art.; Wilson, Martha, 1947-; Franklin Furnace (Archive)
- Series I: Journals, 1969-2017
  - Subseries A: Journals
    - Loose Diary with enclosures December 1, 1969 to February 5, 2010, 1969-1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Journal September 8, 1972 to March 4, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Journal June 22, 1972 to March 30, 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Journal April 2, 1974 to March 30, 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Weekly Planner 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Journal February 1974 to October 5, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Journal February 22, 1975 to June 29, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Business Diary 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Journal August 4, 1975 to March 6, 1976, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Journal February 19,1976 to January 5, 1977, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Journal December 25, 1976 to June 5, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Journal January 1, 1977 to September 19, 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Journal January 1, 1977 to December 27, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Journal September 29, 1978 to September 20, 1979, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Journal March 7, 1979 to October 19, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Loose journal entries August 14, 1979 to August 18, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Journal October 18, 1979 to December 21, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Journal December 23, 1979 to April 4, 1980, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Journal January 27, 1980 to April 11, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Journal March 24, 1980 to March 13, 1981, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Journal April 26, 1980 to June 11, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Journal [May 12, 1980 to June 16, 1980] (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Journal June 18, 1980 to November 14, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Journal September 27, 1980 to November 27, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Journal December 8, 1980 to July 13, 1983, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Journal May 18, 1981 to August 3, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Journal August 3, 1981 to August 17, 1994, 1981-1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Journal July 25, 1981 to April 19, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Journal April 20, 1982 to June 16, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Journal November 16, 1981 to May 22, 1982, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Journal August 20, 1982 to March 27, 1983, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Journal October 21, 1982 to January 10, 1983, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Journal February 3, 1983 to [April 1983], 1983 to [1893] (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Journal March 15, 1983 to April 20, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Journal March 27, 1983 to March 1, 1984, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Journal July 29, 1983 to December 27, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Journal January 23, 1984 to March 30, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Journal March 4, 1984 to June 13, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Journal March 7, 1984 to May 17, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Journal May 21, 1984 to June 30, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Journal July 1, 1984 to August 19, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - notepad Journal [July 12, 1984] to 1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Journal June 15, 1984 to July 13, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Journal August 21, 1984 to August 24, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Journal August 22, 1984 to November 5, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Journal October 5, 1984 to November 14, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - notepad Journal October 12, 1984 to December 6, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Journal [November 14, 1984] (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Journal July 15, 1984 to August 20, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Journal September 15, 1984 to October 1, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Journal December 18, 1984 to March 14, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Journal January 24, 1985 to May 23, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Journal April 24, 1985 to June 4, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Journal June 6, 1985 to July 9, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Journal August 19, 1985 to September 19, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Journal September 1, 1985 to September 27, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Journal November 1, 1985 to [December 11, 1985] (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Journal January 1, 1986 to June 18, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Journal March 20, 1986 to June 21, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Journal undated to December 15, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Journal December 24, 1986 to January 6, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Journal January 8, 1986 to November 11, 1987, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Journal February 1, 1987 to March 23, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Journal November 14, 1987 to undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Journal March 22, 1989 to March 11, 1990, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Journal May 11, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Journal July 2, 1990 to September 17, 1991, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Journal November 1, 1991 to August 13, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Journal June 28, 1992 to June 2, 1999, 1992-1999 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Journal October 27, 1994 to November 9, 1996, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Journal January 3, 1996 to June 12, 1999, 1996-1999 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Journal September 23, 1997 to January 5, 1999, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Journal May 3, 1998 to September 21, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Mommy's trip to Quebec, October 21-27, 1998, Banff Center for the Arts, May 15-16, 1999, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Journal January 9, 1998 to June 12, 1999, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Journal June 18, 1999 to November 16, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Journal November 17, 1999 to May 28, 2000, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Journal May 8, 2000 to October 7, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Restaurant and Journal, August 19, 2000 to November 25, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Journal January 24, 2001 to August 11, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Journal April 1, 2001 to June 22, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Journal August 12, 2001 to November 30, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Journal November 2001 to March 2, 2002, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Journal March 2, 2002 to July 8, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Journal August 13, 2002 to December 15, 2002, Comley's Poetry Notebook (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Journal December 16, 2002 to April 23, 2003, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Journal April 25, 2003 to June 2003, Comley Wilson School Journal Dec 15, 1998 to January 19, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Journal June 12, 2003 to September 11, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Journal September 13, 2003 to January 3, 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Journal January 4, 2004 to May 2, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Journal May 4, 2004 to September 5, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Journal September 5, 2004-February 22, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Journal February 23, 2005 to July 13, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Journal July 14, 2005 to May 15, 2006, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Journal July 25, 2005 to September 2005 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Journal May 17, 2006 to November 17, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Journal June 27, 2006 to March 17, 2007, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Journal November 11, 2006 to May 20, 2007, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Journal May 20, 2007 to October 31, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Journal November 1, 2007 to May 2, 2008, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Journal May 2, 2008 to August 25, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Journal August 25, 2008 to January 3, 2009, 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Journal January 3, 2009 to May 27, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Journal March 26, 2009 to November 8, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Journal November 8, 2009 to June 9, 2010, 2009-2010 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Journal June 2, 2010 to January 8, 2011, 2010-2011 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Journal January 9, 2011 to September 28, 2011 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Journal September 9, 2011 to April 8, 2012, 2011-2012 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Journal November 6, 2011 to April 19, 2012, 2011-2012 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Journal April 25, 2012 to September 12, 2012 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Journal September 12, 2012 to January 20, 2013, 2012-2013 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Journal January 20, 2013 to December 12, 2013 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Journal August 3, 2013 to December 27, 2013 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Journal January 1, 2014 to July 31, 2014 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Journal June 11, 2016 to April 23, 2017, 2016-2017 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Journal April 23, 2017 to December 20, 2017 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Undated Journal (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Undated Journal (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Undated Address Book (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - 2017 Accretion: Diary, 2014-2015 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - 2017 Accretion: Diary, 2015 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - 2017 Accretion: Diary, 2015 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - 2017 Accretion: Diary, December 26, 2015 to June 7, 2016, 2015-2016 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - 2020 Accretion: Journal, June 19, 2015 to May 15, 2017, 2015-2017 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - 2020 Accretion: Journal, December 21, 2017 to June 3, 2018, 2017-2018 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - 2020 Accretion: Journal, June 6, 2018 to March 23, 2019, 2018-2019 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - 2020 Accretion: Journal, July 11, 2018 to November 1, 2019, 2018-2019 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Journal: Donald J. Trump, 2019 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - 2023 Accretion: Journal, November 4, 2019 - April 14, 2020 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - 2023 Accretion: Journal, April 15, 2020 - September 13, 2020 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - 2023 Accretion: Journal, September 5, 2020 - July 22, 2021 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Subseries B: Appointment Calendars
    - Appointment Calendar 1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Appointment Calendar 1994 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Appointment Calendar 1995 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Appointment Calendar 1995 January to May (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Appointment Calendar June 1995 to January 1996, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Appointment Calendar 1996 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Appointment Calendar 1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Appointment Calendar 1998 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Appointment Calendar 1999 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Appointment Calendar 2000 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Appointment Calendar 2001 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Appointment Calendar 2002 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Appointment Calendar 2003 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Appointment Calendar 2004 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Appointment Calendar 2005 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Series II: Correspondence, 1964-2013
  - Subseries A: General Correspondence
    Scope and Contents
    Subseries A contain one or two items. There is a signficant amount of correspondence from Wilson's sister Callie Wilson, and also from her parents.
    Other people well-respresented in the correspondence include: Jerry Allyn, Tonia Aminoff, Jacki Apple, Anton Van Dalen, David Dunlap, Illona Granet, Marc Harrison, Donna Henes, Pieter Holstein, Glena Hydler, Tehching Hsieh, Richards Jardin, Sharon Kulick, Stephanie Brody Lederman, Joni Mabe, Susan Mogul, Linda Montano, Penny and Bob Morris, Alyson Pou, Barbara Quinn, Marcia Ross, Erin Rumm, Lucy Wilson Sherman, Harley Spillers, Annie Sprinkle, Diane Torr.
    Arrangement
    For the most part, correspondence was not sorted or arranged when it was received by the Fales Library. Correspondence in Subseries A is arranged alphabetically by last name where available, and by first name or initial where no last name was provided. "Illegible" or "unsigned" correspondence is labeled as such.
    - 2twice Arts Foundation, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - 37th birthday invitation, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      General
      copies, some returned and some annotatited of Wilson's birthday invitation announcing her name change to Martha Redy Story.
    - A, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - A, 1995-2000 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - A, David, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - ABC No Rio (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Aballea, Martine, 1976-2005 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Abby, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Abrams, Bonita and Ron, 1983-2003, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Abrams, Benita, 1989-1997, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Abrams, Linsey, 1984-1988 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Acierno, Lou/Dapartment of Cultural Affairs, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Adam, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Adams, Moira, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Adams, Nancy, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Adele/ Green Gorillas (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Adelsic, James, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Agriturismo Cretaiole, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Alan, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Alan and Betty, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - [Alen], undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Alex, 1996-2000 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Alex, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Alex, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Alexander, Kay, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Alice, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Alice, undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Alison, Tom, Kyle and Maddy, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Allan, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Allyn, Jerri, 1983-2007 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Ally (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - [Alosteir and Hilary], undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Alternatives to Marriage Project/ Marshall Miller and Dorian Solot, 1998-2006 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Amass, Katelyn, undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Ame, date illegible (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - American Association of Museums, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - American Civil Liberties Union Censorship Project, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - American Civil Liberties Union newsletter, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - The American Federation of Arts/ Mi Jin Hong, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - America's Funniest Home Videos, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Aminoff, Tania, 1978-2000 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Amos, Emma, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Amy and Mike, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Anastasia, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Amy and Fred, undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Anderson, Ally and Jack Spivy, 1989-1998 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Anderson, David, undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Anderson, Laurie, 1987-1998 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Anderson, Max and Jacqueline, undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Anderson, Maxwell, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Androccio, Carol, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Angelopoulos, Elaine, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Andy and Scott, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Ann, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 52)